en:
  humanizer:
    validation:
      error: You're not a human
    questions:
      - question: "Two plus four?"
        answers: ["6", "six"]
      - question: "Two plus two?"
        answers: ["4", "four"]
      - question: "Seven plus seven?"
        answers: ["14", "fourteen"]
      - question: "five plus five?"
        answers: ["10", "ten"]
      - question: "Jack and Jill went up the..."
        answer: hill
      - question: "What is the number before twelve?"
        answers: ["11", "eleven"]
      - question: Five times two is what?
        answers: ["10", "ten"]
      - question: "Insert the next number in this sequence: 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, .."
        answers: ["15", "fifteen"]
      - question: "Insert the next number in this sequence: 22, 24, 26, 28, .."
        answers: ["30", "thirty"]
      - question: "What is five times five?"
        answers: ["25", "twenty-five"]
      - question: "Ten divided by two is what?"
        answers: ["5", "five"]
      - question: What day comes after Monday?
        answer: "tuesday"
      - question: What is the last month of the year?
        answer: "december"
      - question: How many minutes are in an hour?
        answers: ["60", "sixty"]
      - question: What is the opposite of down?
        answer: "up"
      - question: What is the opposite of north?
        answer: "south"
      - question: What is the opposite of bad?
        answer: "good"
      - question: What is 4 times four?
        answers: ["16", "sixteen"]
      - question: What number comes after 20?
        answers: ["21", "twenty-one"]
      - question: What is the number after 68?
        answers: ["69", "sixty-nine"]
      - question: Which year comes after 2010?
        answer: "2011"
      - question: What month comes before August?
        answer: "july"
      - question: What month comes before July?
        answer: "june"
      - question: What month comes before June?
        answer: "may"
      - question: What month comes before May?
        answer: "april"
      - question: What month comes before April?
        answer: "march"
      - question: What is fifteen divided by three?
        answer: ["five", "5"]
      - question: What is 14 minus 4?
        answers: ["10", "ten"]
      - question: "What comes next? Sunday, Monday, Tuesday.."
        answer: "Wednesday"  
      - question: "What comes next? Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday.."
        answer: "Thursday"
      - question: "What comes next? Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday.."
        answer: "Friday"
      - question: "What comes next? Wednesday, Thursday, Friday.."
        answer: "Saturday"
  
